Visual encodings are mapping from data to display elements.
يتم ترميز الترميزات المرئية من البيانات لعرض العناصر.
Display elements include position on the x axis or y axis,
تتضمن عناصر العرض الموضع على محور x أو محور y،
the size of points or bars,
حجم النقاط أو الأشرطة
the shape of points,
وشكل النقاط
texture, angle, length and many more.
والملمس والزاوية والطول وغير ذلك الكثير.
The question is, how to take our data and
يتمثل السؤال في كيفية أخذ بياناتنا
best display it to an audience using these elements.
وعرضها بشكل أفضل للجمهور باستخدام هذه العناصر.
Researchers have studied how to best convey
درس الباحثون كيفية نقل البيانات بشكل أفضل
data so that an audience understands the message.
حتى يفهم الجمهور الرسالة.
Two of the most effective methods for showing
يتمثل اثنان من الطرق الأكثر فعالية لعرض
quantitative data are the position along an axis, and length.
البيانات الكمية في الموضع على المحور، والطول.
Therefore, creating visualizations that are
لذلك، من المهم جدًا إنشاء تصورات
accurate in these encodings is really important.
دقيقة في هذه الترميزات.
Additionally, humans are drawn strongly to contrast in color.
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، ينجذب البشر بقوة نحو التناقض في اللون.
So color should be reserved for drawing the eye of your audience to a key finding,
لذلك يجب حجز اللون لرسم عين جمهورك إلى نتيجة رئيسية،
and not for differing the bars of a bar chart with no message as shown here.
وليس لاختلاف أشرطة المخطط الشريطي بدون رسالة كما هو موضح هنا.
These colors do nothing for providing context of the underlying data.
هذه الألوان لا تفعل شيئا لتوفير سياق البيانات المهمة.
Here, you can see an appropriate use of color for
هنا، يمكنك رؤية استخدام مناسب للون
identifying the difference between different distributions of points.
لتحديد الفرق بين التوزيعات المختلفة للنقاط.
The color highlights the difference for the audience to quickly understand.
يسلط اللون الضوء على الفرق لفهم الجمهور بسرعة.
Charts that have arching angles or compare based on areas can easily deceive us.
يمكن للمخططات التي تحتوي على زوايا قوسية أو مقارنة على أساس المناطق خداعنا بسهولة.
You commonly see angles based on areas in a pie chart or pie type charts.
ترى عادةً الزوايا استنادًا إلى مناطق في مخطط دائري أو مخططات من النوع الدائري.
You actually saw a chart that was deceiving in terms of area
لقد رأيت في الواقع مخططًا خادعًا من حيث المساحة
and angles in the introduction video of this lesson.
والزوايا في فيديو المقدمة لهذا الدرس.
In the next concepts,
في المفاهيم التالية،
we will put these to practice and see what makes a good visual.
سوف نضعها للممارسة ونرى ما يؤدي إلى عرض بصري جيد.